(Howard:)Really? Why?
(Raj:)They exist
in case we ever make contact
(Raj:)with an alien civilization.
(Howard:)Mm, boy, that's one of those
jobs that's boring, boring,
boring, then, "Oh, God!
(Howard:)Where's the memo
with what we do now?!"
(phone chimes)
(Raj:)Oh, this is cool.
(Raj:)So, a few weeks ago,
I set up a fan page
(Raj:)on Facebook for our band and...
Wait a second.
(Howard:)How could you do that
without consulting me?
(Raj:)It's not a big deal.
(Raj:)It just took, like,
five minutes to set up.
(Howard:)That's not the point.
(Howard:)When we created
Footprints on the Moon,
(Howard:)we agreed that every band
decision would be mutual.
(Howard:)Now you're just trying to
take over the whole thing.
(Amy:)You know,
maybe I should go solo.
(Raj:)But someone joined
our page.
(Raj:)We have an actual fan.
(Howard:)All right.
(Howard:)This thing's bigger than you
and me... band's back together.
(Raj:)So, listen to what he wrote.
Uh, "I saw you play
at the comic book store.
You guys rock."
(Raj:)And then there's
a animated smiley face